

 
   //Questions array
            let questions = [
            {
                 number:1,
                 question: "What defines blockchain technology?",
                 answer : "Decentralized,Distributed Ledger System",
                 options : [
                                  "Centralized Ledger System",
                                  "Decentralized,Distributed Ledger System",
                                  "Localized Data Storage System ",
                                  "Hierarchical Data Structure"
                                ]
								
            },
            {
                 number:2,
                 question: "How does Artificial Intelligence(AI)impact industries??",
                 answer : "Automates tasks and improves efficiency",
                 options : [
                                  "Slows down processes",
                                  "Reduces data analysis ",
                                  "Automates tasks and improves efficiency",
                                  "Limits innovation possibilities"  
                                  ]
          
            },
           {
                 number:3,
                 question: "What is the primary advantage of 5G technology??",
                 answer : "Faster data transfer rates and lower latency",
                 options : [ 
                                  "Slower data transfer rates",
                                  "Higher latency",
                                  "Limited connectivity",
                                  "Faster data transfer rates and lower latency"
                                  ]
            
            },
            {
                 number:4,
                 question: "How do quantum computers differ from classical computers?",
                 answer : "They use qubits and perform exponentially faster calculations",
                 options : [
                                  "They use bits for calculations",
                                  "They perform calculations at a slower pace",
                                  "They use qubits and perform exponentially faster calculations",
                                  "They are limited to simple computations"
                                  ]
								  
            }, 
            {
                 number:5,
                 question: "What does the Internet of Things (IoT) enable?",
                 answer : "Remote monitoring, data collection, and automation",
                 options : [ 
                                  "Connectivity only in urban areas",
                                  "Remote monitoring, data collection, and automation",
                                  "Limited device compatibility",
                                  "Exclusive use in industrial settings"
                               ]
							   
            },
            {
                 number:6,
                 question: "What is one of the ethical concerns in biotechnology advancements?",
                 answer : "Potential misuse of gene editing technologies",
                 options : [
                                  "Lack of innovation",
                                  "Limited use in healthcare",
                                  "Potential misuse of gene editing technologies",
                                  "Ethical acceptance worldwide"
                               ]
							   
            },
            {
                 number:7,
                 question: "How are renewable energy technologies evolving?",
                 answer : "Through innovations in efficiency and storage",
                 options : [
                                  "They are becoming less efficient",
                                  "They are becoming more expensive",
                                  "Through innovations in efficiency and storage",
                                  "They are losing popularity"
                               ]
						
            },
             {
                 number:8,
                 question: "What is a challenge in the adoption of autonomous vehicles?",
                 answer : "Safety concerns and ethical dilemmas",
                 options : [
                                 "Lack of regulatory hurdles",
                                 "High level of public acceptance",
                                 "Safety concerns and ethical dilemmas",
                                 "No need for infrastructure updates"
                               ]
							   
			 },
            {
                 number:9,
                 question: "What defines augmented reality (AR)??",
                 answer : "Overlaying digital information onto the real world",
                 options : [
                                 "Replacement of reality with digital information",
                                 "Overlaying digital information onto the real world",
                                 "Limited applications in gaming",
                                 "Irrelevant in the healthcare industry"
                               ]     
  				   
		   },
            {
                 number:10,
                 question: "How does biometric technology impact security and privacy?",
                 answer : "Raises concerns about data privacy",
                 options : [
                                 "Reduces security measures",
                                 "Raises concerns about data privacy",
                                 "Increases data vulnerability",
                                 "Minimizes identification accuracy"
                               ]
							   
            }
             ];    